Nationally, one in six children miss 15 or more days of school in a year.
在全国范围内，每六个孩子中就有一个一年缺课15天或以上。
Education officials have deplored all this missed instruction.
教育官员一直对学生落下这么多课深感痛惜。
These chronically absent students suffer academically because of all the classroom instruction they miss out on.
这些长期缺课的学生由于错过了那么多课堂教学，学业受到了损害。
In 2015, the US secretary of education responded to this crisis, urging communities to support every student to attend every day and be successful in school.
2015年，美国教育部长对这一危机作出回应，敦促各社区支持每一名学生天天到校、学业有成。
His open letter stated that missing 10% of school days in a year for any reason—excused or unexcused—is a primary cause of low academic achievement.
他在公开信中指出，一年中缺课达到上学天数的10%，无论出于何种原因，也无论是请过假的还是无故的，都是学业成绩低下的一个主要原因。
Worrying about whether children attend school makes sense.
担心孩子有没有上学，是有道理的。
After all, if students don’t show up, teachers can’t teach them.
毕竟，学生不来上学，老师就没法教他们。
But what if America’s attendance crisis is about much more than students missing class?
但如果美国的出勤危机远不止学生缺课这么简单呢？
What if, instead, it is a reflection of family and community crises these students face—such as being ejected from the family apartment, fearing for their safety in their neighborhood or suffering an illness?
要是它其实反映的是这些学生所面临的家庭和社区危机呢？比如被赶出家里的公寓、在自己住的街区为自身安全担忧，或是身患疾病。
As social scientists we investigated how excused and unexcused absences relate to children’s academic achievement.
作为社会科学家，我们研究了请过假的缺课和无故缺课与孩子的学业成绩有何关系。
We find that absences excused by a parent do little to harm children’s learning.
我们发现，经家长请假的缺课对孩子的学习几乎没有损害。
In fact, children with no unexcused absences—but 15 to 18 excused absences—have test scores equal to those of their peers who have no absences.
事实上，没有无故缺课、但请过假缺课15至18次的孩子，考试成绩与一次课都没缺过的同龄人相同。
Meanwhile, the average child with even just one unexcused absence does much worse academically than peers with none.
而平均而言，哪怕只有一次无故缺课的孩子，学业表现也比没有无故缺课的同龄人差得多。
We believe unexcused absence is a strong signal of the many challenges children and families face, including economic and medical hardships.
我们认为，无故缺课是一个强烈的信号，表明孩子和家庭面临着诸多挑战，包括经济上和医疗上的困难。
Unexcused absences can be a powerful signal of how those out-of-school challenges affect children’s academic progress.
无故缺课可以作为一个有力的信号，揭示那些校外挑战如何影响孩子的学业进展。
Our evidence suggests unexcused absences are problematic, but for a different reason than people often think.
我们的证据表明，无故缺课是个问题，但原因和人们常常以为的不一样。
Absence from school, and especially unexcused absence, matters mainly as a signal of many crises children and their families may be facing.
缺课，尤其是无故缺课，其意义主要在于它是一个信号，表明孩子及其家庭可能正面临诸多危机。
It matters less as a cause of lower student achievement due to missed instruction.
至于缺课让学生落下课程、进而导致成绩较差，这方面的意义则要小一些。
How we choose to think of school absences matters for educational policy.
我们选择如何看待缺课，这对教育政策来说很重要。
School attendance policies typically hold schools and families accountable for the days children miss, regardless of whether they were excused or unexcused absences.
学生考勤政策通常要求学校和家庭为孩子缺课的天数负责，而不管这些缺课是请过假的还是无故的。
These policies assume that missing school for any reason harms children academically because they are missing classroom instruction.
这些政策假定，无论出于何种原因缺课，孩子都会因错过课堂教学而学业受损。
They also assume that schools will be able to effectively intervene by reducing student absences.
它们还假定，学校能够通过减少学生缺课来有效干预。
We find neither to be the case.
我们发现，这两种假定都不成立。
As a result, these attendance policies end up disproportionately punishing families dealing with out-of-school crises in their lives and pressuring schools that serve them to get students to school more often.
因此，这些考勤政策最终会不成比例地惩罚那些生活中正在应对校外危机的家庭，并向为这些家庭服务的学校施压，要求它们提高学生的出勤率。
We instead suggest using unexcused absence from school as a signal to channel resources to the children and families who need them most.
我们建议换一种做法：把无故缺课当作一个信号，据此将资源输送给最需要这些资源的孩子和家庭。